Christine Kiyabu UI Designer

Los Angeles, CA

Contact Details

(123) 456-7890 ChristineKiyabu@gmail.com Portfolio coming soon

EDUCATION

UI Design | 2021

Career Foundry

- 11 month/500+ hours intensive training program with industry-leading mentors. Studies spanned from visual design principles, color theory, grids, and UI/UX best practices to wireframing, prototyping, responsive design, mobile gestures, and animated interactions.

Cosmetology License | 2015

KC Beauty Academy

BA Psychology | 2012

University of California, Santa Barbara

PROFILE

UI designer with a diverse background, ranging from a psychology degree and experience in sales strategy, to a creative and visual design-focused background in cosmetology and wedding planning.

Accurately assesses individual's needs and creates aesthetically functional UI design by combining both the fascination for the human response with an eye for creativity.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Strategy Administrative Assistant | Apr 2018 - Present

Wismettac Asian Foods Inc (Santa Fe Springs, CA)

- Designs and creates all marketing material to present to customers (e.g. sell sheets, brochures, trade show materials, company & product presentations)
- Designs Asian food product packages targeted at mainstream customers
- Redesigns sales strategy for Asian convenience stores to effectively display products

Behavioral Therapist | May 2016 - May 2017

Center for Autism & Related Disorders (Los Angeles, CA)

- Designed fun activities while implementing behavioral intervention programs to prompt interactive success

Bridal Hair & Makeup Artist | Jan 2016 - May 2017

Kelly Zhang Studio (Pasadena, CA)

- Performed professional bridal makeup on 150+ clients throughout California

Wedding Planner | Jul 2013 - Nov 2013

Kanalu Weddina (Honolulu, HI)

- Multi-tasked to organize and plan every aspect of client weddings, from creating financial estimates to coordinating with multiple vendors

SKILLS

Sketch, Photoshop, InVision, Marvel, Flinto, UsabilityHub, Microsoft Office, Shelf Logic **Tools**

User Interface, Wireframing, Branding, User Stories/Personas, User Research, User Testing/ Analysis, Prototyping

Design